안녕 애들아
Hey, guys...
잠깐. 내가 말할래
wait, let me tell them.
그래 그럼
Sure.
조이가 게임프로에 초대손님으로 출연한대
Joey's going to be a celebrity guest on a game show.
오~!
Oh.
정말? 무슨 프로?
Really? Which one?
잠깐! 물고기, 해초, 난파선...
Fish. Seaweed. A sunken ship.
'바다에서 찾을 수 있는 것'
"피라미드"쇼에 나간다말야?
'Things you find in the ocean.'You're going to be on pyramid! Oh, it was our favorite game show ever.
내가 제일 좋아하는 게임프론데
- "매치 게임" 빼구
- 아, "승패의 갈림길"
Except for match game. Or win, lose or draw.
으~ 내가 무슨 결혼을 한거야
What did I marry into?
그럼 내일 녹화장에 같이 갈래?
Well, do you guys want to come down tomorrow and watch me tape the show?
안돼, 내일 피비의 처녀파티가 있거든
Oh, we can't. We're throwing Phoebe a bachelorette party.
맞아, 미안해 자리가 없어
남자들은 못끼워주거든
Yeah, sorry, boys. This ride's closing.
챈들러와 나는 지겨운
대학 동창 모임에 가야돼
Well, and Chandler and I have this stupid college alumni thing.
I can't believe you get to meet Donny Osmond.
도니 오스먼드를 만나다니
믿을 수가 없어
정말?
Seriously?
그래
Yuh-huh!
로스랑 나는 항상 '도니'랑
'마리'가 되고 싶어 했거든
Ross and I always wanted to be Donny and Marie.
갈수록 상태가 나빠지네
You guys just keep getting cooler and cooler.
우리가 가족들과 친구들 앞에서
흉내내곤 했었어
We used to perform for our family and friends.
아! 맞아, 내가 계획했었지!
Oh, god, that's right. I blocked that out.
"나는야 컨트리 가수~!"
"I'm a little bit country ~!"
"나는 락앤롤~!"
"and I'm a little bit rock and roll.~!"
우리 끝내자
I'm leaving you.
FㆍRㆍIㆍEㆍNㆍDㆍS
10x11 The One Where The Stripper Cries
[해 석] 박재은(jaeunpark@hotmail.com)
[테스터] 배종혁(jonghyukbae@hotmail.com)
[싱 커] 김병희(reann@korea.com)
임의의 수정 및 상업적 용도의 사용을 금합니다.
자막을 피드백 게시판을 이용해 주세요
(club.korea.com/friends)
사람들을 다시 만나다니
기분이 이상해
It's so weird to see all these people again.
오, 저기 재프리 클락이다
Oh, my god, look, there's Jeffrey Klarik.
누구?
Who?
존 로저프의 룸메이트 있잖아
He was roommates with John Rosoff?
앤드라 템보리노랑 사귀던 애
He went out with Andrea Tamborino?
왜 그녀가 마이클 클로프 때문에
걔를 차버렸잖아
She dumped him for Michael Skloff?
Did I go to this school?
내가 이 학교 다닌거 맞냐?
저기 미시 골드버그가 있다
쟤 기억나니?
Hey, there's Missy Goldberg. You got to remember her.
Sure. Nice. Dude, you're married to my sister.
당연하지, 죽이는데
야, 넌 내 동생이랑 결혼한 몸이야
그래 그래
이쁘다고 말하는 것도 죄가 되냐?
You're right. By saying "nice," I'm virtually licking her.
지금 싱글이라던데
데이트 신청해볼까?
Hey, I hear she's single again. Think I should ask her out?
너 지금 우리의 계약을 해지하는데 대해
내 허락을 구하는거야?
Are you asking permission to break the pact?
그래, 제발~
Yes, please.
헤이, 우리 밴드에 대한
전단지가 나왔어
Hey, check out the fliers for the band.
컴퓨터실에서 매킨토시를
사용해서 만들었어
I made them on a macintosh in the computer room.
죽이는데, 이름이 정말 튄다
Awesome. The name really stands out.
헬비티카체, 24 포인트야
Thanks to a little something called helvetica bold 24 point.
Man, we're going to rock that Asian student union!
안녕, 얘들아
Hey, Missy.
안녕, 미시
우리 밴드가 금요일에 공연하는데
You know, our band is playing on friday.
그래, 너도 꼭 와서 봐
제목이 "Way / No way"야
Yeah, yeah, you should come check us out. We're called "way/no way."
No way
no way.
Way
way.
좋아, 갈게
Great. I'll be there.
신선한데
Fresh.
- 최고야
- 짱이야
Boss.
쿨해
Mint.
갔어
She's gone.
I know it.
나도 알아
있잖아, 그녀에게 꼭
데이트 신청을 해야겠어
You know, I'm totally going to ask her out.
야, 내가 신청하려 했는데
Dude, I was going to ask her out.
형씨, 내가 먼저 말했어
I said it first, bro.
내가 먼저 생각하고 있었어, 홈즈
Oh, I thought it first, Holmes.
Look, if you think...
잠깐, 우리가 뭐하는 짓이지?
Wait, wait. What are we doing?
우리 사이를 여자들 따위로
망칠 순 없어
What we have is too important to mess it up over some girl.
I mean, we can get laid anytime we want.
우린 언제든지 걔들을
넘어뜨릴 수 있어
맞아
Totally.
난 고등학교 때 해봤어
I had sex in high school.
나두.. 난 끝내줬어
Me, too. I'm good at it.
좋아, 우리 계약하자
All right, I say we make a pact.
우리 둘 다 미시 골드버그와
데이트하지 말자
Neither of us will go out with Missy Goldberg.
좋은 생각이야
You got it.
미시 골드버그, 피비 케이츠 몰리 링바트도 포함이야
All right, so that's Missy Goldberg, Phoebe Cates and Molly Ringwald who neither of us can go out with.
약속한거다
Those are the pacts.
아, 쉬나 이스턴도 포함시켜
Oh, and Sheena Easton.
어차피 그녀랑은 안될테니깐
But we probably couldn't get her anyway.
하하.. 넌 안되겠지~
Huh! Huh! Maybe not you.
좋아, 공식적으로 너는
계약을 무시해도 괜찮아
Well, I officially give you permission to break the pact.
고맙다
Thank you.
좋아, 시작해볼까
All right, here I go.
내가 대학 때 여자들 때문에
얼마나 떨었는지 기억나지?
Now, remember how scary it used to be going up to girls in college?
너 지금 떨고 있어
Your hands are shaking.
알아, 식은 땀도 나고 있어
I know, and I can't stop sweating.
...Five, Four, three, applause!
Yeah!
안녕하세요
오늘은 드라마 특집 쇼입니다
Welcome. It is soap opera week here on Pyramid.
오늘의 참가자를 만날까요
Let's meet our contestants.
먼저 데이터 처리 전문가이신
진 레스터와
First, Gene Lester is a database specialist.
함께 하게되는 'Day Of Our Lives'의
스타인 조이 트리비아니 입니다
He's going to be playing with days of our lives star, Joey Tribianni!
and over here we have Henrietta Cherry...
그리고 이쪽은...
일반인이 유명스타와 함께 한다는게
겁난다는 거 압니다, 걱정말아요
Listen, I know it can be intimidating for regular people to be around celebrities, but relax,
난 당신과 같아요
단지 잘생기고 돈많다는거 빼고
I'm just like you, only better-looking and richer.
...'General Hospital'의 스타인 레슬리 찰슨 입니다
...She'll be playing with star of General Hospital, Leslie Charleson...
여러분 안녕하십니까
모두에게 행운를 빌겠습니다
Welcome, everybody. Good luck to all of you. Let's play pyramid. All right.
게임을 시작할까요?
Now, we flipped a coin before the show.
시작 전에 동전던지기로
순서를 정했습니다
진 먼저 시작하세요
카테고리를 선택하십시오
Gene, you won the toss, so you're going to start. Which category would you like?
저는 "선을 넘다" 를 정하겠습니다
I'll take "you crossed the line."
좋습니다, 조이, 다음의 것을 진에게
설명해 주세요, 20초 입니다, 시작
"You crossed the line." Joey, describe for Gene the things that have lines. Give me 20 seconds on the clock, please. Ready. Go.
[수퍼마켓]
음.. 이건 가게인데 수퍼마켓 같은거요
Uh, okay, it's a store like a supermarket...
앗! 알았어요
oh, I see what I did there.
좋아 좋아
Okay, okay.
[노트북]
글 쓰는거요
I'm writing in my...
일기
diary?
아니, 그거 왜 노트북 같은거
No, more like a notebook--
제길!!
damn it!
[청사진]
Um... oh, if I'm building a house, the plan isn't called a shmooprint... I can't do that either?
왜 집을 지을 때 계획 세우는걸
무슨 사진이라 하죠?
이것도 안돼요?
[축구장]
Oh, in high school, I once had sex with a girl right in the middle of the...
고등학교 시절, 여자 친구랑
바로 여기서 섹스하고 싶었는데
카페테리아
cafeteria.
Yeah, but that's not what they're looking for.
여기서 말하는 건 딴곳인데요
이런
oh!
파티 정말 고마워
Thank you so much for this.
Aw... you like it?
어때, 맘에 들어?
너무 우아해
근데 야한 건 언제 나와?
Oh, my god, it's all so elegant. When's the dirty stuff starting?
뭐?
What?
왜 있잖아, 스트립 쇼랑..
남자들이 춤추고 여기저기 오줌누고...
You know, the strippers and the guys dancing and, you know, pee-pees flying about.
Oh!
피비, 그런 건 없는데
Pheebs, I... there isn't going to be any "flying about."
우리 생각엔 그런거 하기엔
좀 늙은 거 같아서
We actually thought we were a little too mature for stuff like that.
알았어, 네가 뭐하는지 알았어
좋아, 차마시는게 다라구?
I see what you're doing. That's fine. This is all there is. Just tea. Okay.
음~ 야하긴
Mmm... raunchy.It's okay.
피비, 정말로 그런거 안할거야
Seriously, pheebs, it's not going to be that kind of party.
뭐라고? 그럼 이게 내
처녀시절의 환송식이란 말야?
Really? So th-this is... this is my big send-off into married life?
레이첼, 이게 내 인생의
한번뿐인 처녀파티란 말야
Rachel, this is the only bachelorette party I'm ever going to have.
돈 뭉치도 챙겨왔는데
정말 이게 다라구 정말?
I've, I've got a big wad of ones in my purse. really? I mean really? It's just tea?
아냐~ 물론 다른게 더 있지
No! Phoebe, of course there's more.
Okay. I mean, let me just go talk to Monica and get an eta on the pee-pees.
내말은 말이지.. 스트리퍼들이
언제 도착하는지 모니카에게 물어볼께
진, 탈락되지 않으려면
여섯개 모두 맞춰야 합니다
Gene, I must remind you, you need all six of these to stay in the game, all right?
[냉장고에서 찾을수 있는 것]에
대해 조이에게 설명해 주세요
Describe for Joey things you find in your refrigerator.
저들이 점수를 주려고 하네요
They might as well just give us the points.
20초입니다, 자 시작~
give me 20 seconds on the clock. Ready. Go.
[크림]
커피에 넣어 마시는거요
You put this in your coffee.
A spoon! Your hands! Your face!
스푼, 손, 얼굴?
하얀색인데
It's white.
종이, 눈, 유령!
Paper! Snow! A ghost!
우유보다 진한거 있잖아요
It's heavier than milk.
바위, 개, 지구?
A rock. A dog. The earth.
다음
Pass.
[마요네즈]
샌드위치에 넣어 먹는거
You put this on a sandwich.
살라미, 앤쵸비, 쨈
Salami. Anchovies. Jam.
하얀색
It's white.
종이, 눈, 유령!
Paper! Snow! A ghost!
계란으로 만드는거
It's made from eggs.
치킨
Chickens!
다음
Pass!
[케찹]
햄버거에 넣어 먹는 것
you put it on a hamburger.
Ketchup!
케찹
Relish!
렐리쉬
그만
Stop!
Oh, time's up.
시간이 다 됐습니다
조이, 성공할 수 있었는데 아쉽네요
Joey, you were almost on a roll there.
진, 당신이 거의 2부 결승전에
진출할 수 있었는데
Gene, you're going to have a chance to go to the winner's circle in the second half,
but right now, Henrietta, you are going to the winner's circle to try your luck for $10,000 right after this.
이젠 헨리에타가 10,000달러
상금을 두고 결승전에 진출합니다
Don't go away. And we're out.
우리가 졌네요
그래도 재밌는 게임이었죠?
Oh, so we didn't win. But it's fun to play the game, right?
Hey, I got a kid starting college. I have to get surgery on my knee.
우리 애가 대학에 입학하려 하고
나는 무릎 수술을 받아야 합니다
근데 지금 당신이
10,000달러를 날려버렸어요
You just lost me ten grand.
I'm so sorry. Okay, I promise, we'll do better next time.
죄송해요, 다음번엔 더 잘할께요
걱정마쇼, 다음에는
당신과 같이 게임안할 거니깐
Well, I will, because I won't be playing with you.
정말 어려운 문제들이었단 말이예요
대체 왜 냉장고에 유령이 있겠어요?
You know, some of those were pretty hard. Like, why would there be a ghost in my fridge?
Yeah.
그럼 토요일 저녁 어때?
So, Saturday night?
좋아
I'd love to.
Great.
나한테 데이트 신청하는데
그렇게 오랜 세월이 걸렸어?
So how come it took you so long to ask me out?
그게 좀 바보같아
내 룸메이트 챈들러 알지?
Oh, well, uh, this is going to sound kind of silly, but... Do you remember my roommate Chandler Bing?
물론이지
너랑 같은 '밴드부'였던
Sure. He was in your "band."
16년이 지나도
그 밴드에 대해 놀리면 민망해
It's been 16 years, but the air quotes still hurt.
미안
Sorry.
괜찮아, 어쨌든 걔랑 나
둘 다 너를 좋아했었거든
Anyway, well, he and I both really liked you a lot, um,
그래서 우리의 우정을 망치지 않으려고
약속을 했어, 너에게 데이트신청 안하기로
but we didn't want anything to jeopardize your friendship, so we kind of made a pact that neither of us could ask you out.
정말?
Really?
왜 그러는데?
Yeah. Why?
Well, Chandler and I used to make out... a lot.
난 챈들러랑 만나곤 했는데
정말?
You did?
수업끝나고 과학 실험실에 가곤 했는데
Yeah. We'd go to the science lab after hours.
날 따돌리고?
And on my turf?!
Hey, where is this guy? It's been over an hour.
한시간이나 지났는데
이 사람 언제오는거야?
Well, he's coming from Jersey.
저지에서 오는 중이야
최대한 빨리 온다고 했어
He said he would get here as fast as he could.
누구세요?
Who is it?
경찰입니다
It's the police.
경찰이래!!
The police!
That's right, it's officer goodbody.
몸짱 경찰입니다
무슨 일이시죠? 경관님
나쁜 일이 생겼나요?
What's the matter, officer, has someone been bad?
Whoo, that' a lot of stairs.
후우.. 계단이 정말 많군
Hoo, boy.
엘리베이터가 없다고
미리 이야기 했어야죠
You should warn people there's no elevator.
Whoa, oh... I should not have had that Mexican food for lunch.
점심에 멕시칸 음식을
먹는게 아니었는데
Are-are you gonna be okay, officer, uh...
괜찮으세요? 어...
몸짱요
goodbody.
아, 네...
If you say so.
그럼 어느 숙녀분이
내 유혹을 받는거요?
So, where's the young lady who I am supposed to take... downtown?
오 맙소사
Oh, god.
All right, somebody show me where to plug in my box,
어디에 전원이 있지?
자, 파티를 시작해 볼까요
and we'll get this party started.
우~ 와우!
Wah!
어디요? 좋아요
Where? All right.
레이첼
Rachel?
응?
Yeah?
너 지금 장난하니?
Um, are you kidding?
우린 네가 스트립쇼를
원하는 지 몰랐어
All right, look, we did not know that you wanted a stripper, so we went to the phone book,and we got the first name we could find.
그래서 전화번호부에서
찾은 곳으로 전화했는데
그 전화번호부 얼마나 오래됐니?
How old's your phone book?!
오 세상에, 내 아파트에서
그가 옷을 벗을꺼야
Oh, my god, this man is gonna get naked in my apartment.
Oh, no, I don't want to see him take his clothes off.
난 그가 스트립하는거 보기싫어
Are you talking about me?
지금 내 얘기하는거요?
아뇨, 우린 지금 당신의 스트립쇼를
꼭 보고 싶다고 이야기하는 중이에요
I mean, obviously, we want to see you take your clothes off... you big piece of eye candy.
Okay, okay, ladies, can I have your attention, please?
좋아요, 여기 주목해 주세요
누가 법의 손길을 필요로 합니까?
Did someone call for the long arm of the law? I should warn you, I have a concealed weapon.
내 미리 경고하지만
나는 숨겨진 무기가 있습니다
처벌에 놀라지 않기를 바래요
I hope you're familiar with this state'S... penal code.
Okay, okay, enough teasin'. Now for some pleasin'.
서론은 이만하고
본론으로 들어갈까요
진력난 표정이잖아
She cringed!
This is how I look when I'm turned on.
난 흥분할 때 이런 표정을 지어요
아까 나에 대해서 이야기 했던거죠?
You were talking about me before.
그만 둡시다, 난 가겠어요
내 모자가 어디있지?
Look, I don't need this. I'm out of here. Where's my hat?
난 이 일을 오랫동안 했어요
Look, I've been in this business for a long time.
놀랍군요
Shocking.
내 300달러를 주면 난 돌아가겠소
Now if you'll just pay me my $300, I'll be on my way.
300달러? 당신 제 정신이에요?
$300? Are you kidding?
아냐 아냐, 내 수표책 좀 줘봐
No, that's okay, let me just get my checkbook.
No, you're not gonna pay him--he didn't do anything.
그에게 돈 줄 필요 없어
아무 것도 안했는데
아무 짓도 안했다고?
Didn't do anything? I took a bus all the way from Hoboken. I climbed, I don't know, like, a billion stairs.
버스를 타고 여기까지 왔고
저 많은 계단을 올라왔는데
그건 아무 것도 아니요?
And it's not like I can take them two at a time.
상관 없어요
I don't care
어쨌든 우리는 300달러 못줘요
we're not paying you $300 for this.
여보쇼, 당신이 너무 까다로워서
Well, look, it's not my fault
이 남자다움의 극치에
만족하지 않는건 내 잘못이 아니요
if you're too uptight to appreciate the male form in all its glory.
맞아요, 난 까다로워요
Oh, yeah, okay, I'm uptight.
그래서 애들 할로윈 의상같은 옷을 입은
아저씨가 춤추는 건 보기 싫다는 거에요
Yeah, that's why I don't want to watch a middle-aged guy dance around in what I can only assume is a child's halloween costume.
옷은 내 조카에게 빌리긴 했어도
내 장담하건데 옷 안에 있는건 '남자'요
I may have borrowed this from my nephew... but let me assure you, what's underneath is all man.
늙은이가 아니구요?
I'm sorry, did you say "all man" or "old man"?
Oh... you're mean.
당신은 심술궂군요
Uh, look, officer, uh, sir...
경관님, 선생님
제기랄
damn it! Oh...
고깃덩어리도 감정이 있다니깐
놀라워요?
big surprise: The hunk of beef has feelings.
헨리에타, [잭과 질이
언덕위로 올라가다]를 골랐습니다
Okay, Henrietta, you picked "Jack and Jill went up the hill."
제 친구 레이첼에게 아이가 있는데요
전 양육에 관해서 빠삭해요
My friend Rachel has a kid. I totally know nursery rhymes.
조이, 미국 의회과 관련된
다음의 것들을 설명하십시오
Joey, describe these things associated with the united states congress.
20초입니다, 시작하세요
Give me 20 seconds on the clock, please.
[주의회]
으.. 어~ 어
Uh... uh...
다음
Pass.
[미국회의사당]
다음
Pass.
[의사방해연설자]
다음
Pass.
[추가]
Okay, the little thing that hangs down in the back of your throat.
목에 달려 있는 것
목젓
A uvula.
Oh. Then pass.
다음
시간됐습니다
Okay.
헨리에타, 점수가 모자르군요
Henrietta, you didn't get all the points you needed, so that means, Gene, you are going to the winner's circle to try for $10,000,
그러면 진, 당신이 10,000달러
결승전에 오르게 됩니다
조이 트리비아니와 함께
게임을 하게됩니다
and you're gonna be going there with Joey Tribbiani!
너 미시 골드버그와
데이트 했었다며?
You made out with Missy Goldberg? How could you do that after you promised me?
나랑 약속해놓고 어떻게 그럴수 있어?
실례합니다
Excuse me.
우리가 게이들 같게 들리지 않았지?
That didn't make us sound gay at all.
넌 계약을 어겼어
You broke the pact!
로스, 그건 16년 전 일이야
Ross, that was 16 years ago.
상관없어, 난 지금 우리
우정에 대해서 이야기하는거야
That doesn't matter. We're talking about the foundation of our friendship.
내 생각에 우리 우정은 우스꽝스런
헤어스타일에서 시작한 거 같은데
I believe the foundation of our friendship was unfortunate hair.
좋아, 그렇다면 넌 계약을
어긴 적이 없단 말야?
All right, look, if we're really gonna do this, it's not like you never broke one of the pacts.
어긴 적 없어
I didn't.
정말 그래?
Oh, really?
No!
그래
Oh, really?
정말?
없다니까!
No!
에이드리안 터너
Adrienne Turner!
응?
Yes?
안녕, 애드리안
Hey, Adrienne. Hi, Adrienne.
난 에이드리안과 아무 짓 안했어
I never did anything with Adrienne Turner.
그러지마, 너 내가 얼마나
걔를 좋아했는지 알지?
Oh, please-- and you knew how much I liked her.
난 네가 무슨 이야기 하는지
모르겠는데
I don't know what you're talking about.
그러셔?
Really?
1학년 때 파티 기억나?
크리스마스 휴가 전 주에 있었던?
Remember that big party freshman year, a week before Christmas vacation?
그래
I do
그때 네 손님들이 있었잖아
You had some visitors.
진짜 대학 파티라니 믿어지지가 않아
I can't believe we're at a real college party.
나 화장실이 급해
I have to pee so bad.
대학생 남자들은 너무 귀여워
This is so awesome. College guys are so cute.
넌 남자친구 있잖아
Hey, you've got a boyfriend.
알아, 그래도 코리 헤임같은 남자가
키스하자고 하면, 허락할꺼야
I know. But if some guy who looks like corey haim wants to kiss me tonight, I am so gonna let him.
Oh, hey, look. There's Chandler.
저기 챈들러가 있네
You know, that stupid friend of Ross's who said I was fat.
나보고 뚱뚱하다고 했던
로스의 멍청한 친구 기억나지?
You know, I've already lost four pounds.
내가 4파운드나 뺀거 아니?
그럼
You can so totally tell.
그래
I know!
로스 어디 있는지 물어보자
Well, let's see, maybe he knows where Ross is.
헤이, 잘 지냈어?
Hey, how's it going?
어, 너희는...
Aren't you...
그래, 레이첼, 여긴 로스 동생 모니카
추수감사절에 만났었지
yeah, Rachel. And this is Ross's sister monica. We met at thanksgiving.
그래, 잘있었어?
Right. So, how you doing?
아주 좋아
Bitchin'.
안녕, 모니카
Hi, Monica.
안녕, 챈들러
만나서 정말 반갑지 않~아!
Hi, Chandler. It's really nice to see you. Not.
Okay. I'll see if I can find Ross.
그래, 로스 어디있나 찾아볼게
오, 레이첼
저기 콩주머니 의자가 있어
Oh, my god, Rach, beanbag chairs.
내가 저기 앉지 않도록 도와줘
Do not let me sit in one of those. We'll be here for days.
Listen, Adrienne, you can't tell Chandler about this.
에이드리언, 챈들러에게
절대 이야기하면 안돼
Oh, believe me, Ross, I won't be telling anybody about this.
날 믿어, 어느 누구에게도
이야기하지 않을게
좋았어
Cool.
난 네가 아는지 몰랐어
I didn't know you knew about that.
Well, I did, and it hurt.
그래, 꽤 속상했어
그때가 "휴게실에서의 배신"이란
곡을 썼을 때야
That's when I wrote the song, "betrayal in the common room."
미안해
man, I... I'm sorry.
Look... it was a long time ago.
다 지난일인데 뭐
So, uh... I made out with Adrienne, and you made out with Missy.
난 에이드리안
넌 미시랑 데이트 했으니깐
Well, I guess we're even.
그럼 이제 우리 비긴거네
흐음
Mm-hmm.
우리 비긴거지, 그치?
We are even, right?
한가지가 더 있는데
Just one more thing.
그날밤 너한테 너무 화가나서
너한테 갚아주고 싶었어
I was so pissed at you that night that I wanted to get back at you,
그래서 네가 누굴
가장 좋아하는지 생각했어
so I thought, who does Ross like more than anybody?
너 우리 엄마한테 무슨 짓을 한거야?
What did you do to my mom?
너희 엄마 말구
Not her.
나 취한거 같아
I am so drunk.
이상하네, 나도 너랑 똑같이 마셨는데
난 아무렇지도 않은 걸
That's weird-- I've had the same number of beers as you, and I don't feel anything at all.
재밌게 노는 중이니?
So, you girls having fun?
너에게 알려주는데, 난 체중이
4파운드나 줄었다구, 천치야
For your information, ass munch... ...I've lost four pounds.
아마 지금 춤추고 나면
5파운드 빠졌을 걸?
Maybe even five, with all the dancing.
피자 시키신 분?
Did somebody order a pizza?
여기요
Oh, that's me!
내일 SAT 시험 다 봤군
I am so not gonna do good on my SATs tomorrow.
혹시 알아? 내년에 이 학교에 다닐런지
그럼 우리 같이 만날 수 있을텐데
Well, maybe you could go to school here next year, and we could totally hang out.
그래 괜찮은 생각이네, 내가
똑똑해지는 약을 먹는다면 말이지
Oh, yeah, there's a plan. Why don't I just start taking my smart pills now.
미용관련 학위를 받을 수도 있을텐데
Well, maybe you could get in on a beauty scholarship.
거짓말
What a line.
So, where are you applying to?
어느 학교 지원했어?
나는 따뜻한 곳에서
학교를 다니는게 좋아서...
Um, well, you know, I think it's kind of really important that I go somewhere where there's sun, so I'm sort of... hey!
뭐야!
난 대학생이고 밴드부 소속인데
I'm in college, and I'm in a band.
그래, 그럼 좋아
Yeah, okay. Gotta move on...
뭐요? 50살 먹은 스트립 댄서가
우는 거 첨보슈?
What's the matter? You never saw a 50 year-old stripper cry before?
걱정하지 마세요
돈은 지불할게요
You know, it's fine. We will pay you.
No, no, you're right. Who am I kidding? I should've hung up that break-away jock strap years ago.
아니요, 당신들이 맞아요
이 우스꽝스런 스트립 댄서 일은
벌써 그만뒀어야 했어요
이제 난 뭐하죠?
What am I going to do? I mean, this has been my life for 32 years. Taking my clothes off in front of people is all I know.
난 아는 사람들 앞에서
옷벗는 일만 32년동안 해왔는데
Well, wait, no, there's got to be something else that you can do.
다른 할 일이 있을거예요
I mean, what skills do you have?
어떤 기술을 가지고 있죠?
글쎄요, 춤출 줄 알고
I don't know. I can make my pecs dance.
I can pick up a dollar bill with my butt cheeks.
엉덩이로 돈을 집을 수도 있고
I can go to that special place inside me where I feel no shame.
창피해하지 않고
은밀한 것도 할 줄 아는데
사무실에서 하는것 중에서는요?
So maybe something in an office?
아마 스트립댄스를
가르칠 수도 있겠네요
You could .. , you could teach stripping.
You know, share your gift. Pass the torch.
당신의 재능을 나누세요
전수하세요
그리 나쁘지 않네요
You know, actually that is not a bad idea.
내 아파트에서 할 수도 있고
우리 엄마도 상관없다고 하실거예요
I could do it out of my apartment. I don't think my mom would mind.
그럼 되었네요
이제 괜찮으신 거죠?
There you go, You are going to be okay?
Yeah, ye ... this is so weird. You never know when it's going to be your last dance.
기분이 묘하네요
이게 내 마지막 공연이라니
그것도 다 끝내지도 못한
마지막 공연이라니
And I didn't even get a chance to finish it.
끝내세요
Finish it.
뭐라고요?
What?
마지막 공연이요
우리를 위해서 춤 춰주세요
Your last dance. Do it for us.
정말?
Really?
증말?
그럼, 그는 마지막으로
좋아하는걸 할 만한 자격이 있어
He deserves to do the thing he loves one last time.
좋아요, 자 숙녀분들 준비하세요
Okay. All right
Get ready, ladies.
Okay.
너무 화끈한데
Oh, this is so hot!
오, 그만두지 마세요
Oh, no, no. Don't stop.
어쩔 수 없어요
Have to.
결승전에 오신 걸 환영합니다
well, welcome to the winner's circle.
조이, 진, 준비되셨나요?
Joey, Gene, you guys ready?
Yeah. Sure.
- 네 - 물론이죠
Okay. Give me 60 seconds on the clock, please.
60초 드립니다, 시작하세요
[나무의 종류]
Oak, maple, elm, birch.
떡갈, 단풍, 느릅, 자작...
I dunno... types of trees.
글쎄 모르겠는데요
나무의 종류?
[스페인어]
uh... buenos dias, Enchilada. Pavor.
죄송해요, 스페인어는 하나도 몰라요
Oh, I'm I don't know any spanish words.
[타는 것들]
와우
Wow.
성냥, 초...
A match. A candle.
불 끌 때 '후' 부는 것들
Things that go "tsss" when you put them out.
횃불, 모닥불... 소변!
Rch. A bonfire. Uh... your pee.
Things that burn!
타는 것들
[개가 할 만한 말]
난 산책가고 싶어요
내 배를 쓰다듬어주세요
"I'd like to go for a walk." "Scratch my belly."
여보쇼, 무슨 이야기 하는건지
모르겠어요
Dude, dude, I think you're losing it.
나는 털이 나있고, 멍멍 짖어요
"I have fur." "I like to bark."
Oh, oh, oh. What a dog says.
개가 말하는 거예요?
[피자 토핑]
페러로~
Peppero...
피자 토핑! 다음
Pizza toppings! Next!
[슈퍼 모델]
신디크로포드, 크리스티 브링클리
하이디 클룸, 클라우디아 쉬퍼...
Cindy crawford. Kristy BInkley. Hidy Klum, Claudia schiffer. Oh, oh, oh, oh! Christy turlington. Uh, Kate Moss.
크리스티 털링턴, 케이트 모스...
챈들러가 절대 데이트못할 여자들
Girls chandler could never get?
슈퍼모델
Supermodel
어디요?
Where?
Hey, where is Rachel?
레이첼 어디 있어?
피비랑 같이 스트립댄서를
병원에 데려다 주러 갔어
She and Pheobe took the stripper to the hospital.
너 챈들러가 레이첼한테
키스했던 거 알아?
Did you know Chandler kissed Rachel?
정말? 언제?
What? When was this?
1987년, 너희가
우리 학교에 방문했을때
1987. The weekend you guys visited me at school.
Oh my god. That is wild.
세상에 그거 재밌네
Yeah, but it is like millions years ago. So doesn't matter.
이미 오래 전 이야긴데
무슨 상관이야?
나한텐 상관있어
No, it matters to me.
왜?
why?
왜냐면 그날밤이 바로 내가 레이첼과
처음으로 키스한 바로 그 날이니까
Because the night you kissed Rachel was the night I kissed Rachel for the very first time,
너도 그날밤 레이첼과 키스했어?
You kissed that night too?
Two guys at one night.
두 남자랑 같은 날에?
나는 레이첼이 코수술 한 후에나
그러고 다닌 줄 알았는데
Oh, I thought she became a slut after she got her nose fixed.
언제 키스했는데?
Seriously where did this happen?
Okay, after you told me she was passed out in our room,
네가 레이첼이 우리 방에
쓰러져 있다고 말한 다음에
레이첼이 괜찮은지 보러 갔었거든
I went in there to make sure she was all right.
She was lying on my bed ... uhm all buried in people's coats.
내 침대 위에서 코트에
파묻힌채 누워있더라구
이마에 키스하려고 했는데
어두워서 입에다 해버렸었거든
Well, I went to kiss on the forehead.But it was so dark I accidently got her lips.
I started to pull away but then I felt her start kiss me back.
바로 그만두려했는데 갑자기
그녀도 키스를 해오는거야
잠깐이었지만 정말 놀라웠었어
It's only for second, but it was amzaing.
Now that I found you kissed her first.
근데 네가 그녀에게
네가 먼저 키스했었다니
Wait, what bed you said she was on?
그녀가 어느 침대에 누워있었어?
내 침대 위
Mine.
난 레이첼을 내 침대에 눕혔는데
I'm pretty sure I put her on my bed.
아냐, 정말 내 침대 위에 있었어
No, she was definitely on my bed.
내가 그녀랑 키스하고
네 침대 위에 눕혔을거 같냐?
Why would kiss a girl and put her on your bed?
그럼 내 침대 위에 있던 건 누구야?
And then who was on my bed?
으악~!
Oh, Oh Oh ...
그럴 수 없어
No, No, No
맞아~!
Yes!!
네가 코트 더미 아래에 있었어?
You were under the pile of coats?
그 코트 더미가 나였어
I was the pile of coats!
오 세상에
Oh my god!
오빠가 한밤의 미스테리한
키스의 장본인이라구?
You were my midnight mystery kisser?
너랑 한게 레이첼과의
첫 키스라고?
You were my first kiss with Rachel?
오빠가 내 인생의 첫키스였단 말야?
You were my first kiss ever?
내가 누구랑 결혼한거지?
What did I marry into?
이런!